The Open Compute Project
is a vibrant community
that spans the data center
infrastructure worldwide.
Though not a standards body, the
OCP Community forges new technology
norms, fostering an ecosystem where
industry players collaborate in a safe
framework, shaping a versatile
and diverse supply chain.
From startups to hyperscalers, as well as
research, academia, and investors,
the OCP Community is able to reduce
procurement time, research efforts,
expenses, development time, and even
legal complexity for your projects.
Participating in the OCP Community
gives you access to the latest
technologies and talent,
the chance to improve your skills,
and to drive impact in critical
areas like energy efficiency,
cooling, and sustainability.
Join one of the many project
workstreams to help solve
challenges and pioneer solutions,
or serve as a volunteer leader
to help steer the community towards
the industry's ever increasing challenges.
If you're seeking cutting edge
solutions, explore our marketplace
or the library of specifications
and other contributions,
and embrace OCP solutions
in your next endeavor,
or make OCP specifications
part of your next RFP.
Check out the latest solutions at an
OCP Experience Center, or partner
with any of our OCP recognized facilities
or OCP solution providers.
Contribute specifications, design
files, reference architectures,
or software, to help solve the industry's
greatest challenges, building
trust in you and your brand.
Connect at OCP events through
attendance and sponsorship
and embrace OCP’s inclusive open spirit.
Because together we're
stronger, faster, and better.